{"data":[{"question":"I was very interested to read your article for global warming in the newspaper.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"to read","c":"for","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"- For-> on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"I am afraid I don't agree with you on a number of point.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"am","b":"with","c":"on","d":"point","answer":"4","explain":"- Point-> points","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"On the contrary we need to make the public more aware of so danger.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"On","b":"to make","c":"more","d":"so","answer":"4","explain":"- So-> x\/the","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"We most all put pressure on the authorities if we want something be done.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"most all","b":"on the authorities","c":"something","d":"be done","answer":"4","explain":"- Be done-> to be done","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Lastly you seem to suggest doing nothing in of case the scientists are wrong.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Lastly","b":"to suggest","c":"nothing","d":"in of case","answer":"4","explain":"- In of case-> in case of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Well, if they are right, it will be too late by the time we will find out.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"if","b":"will be","c":"by the time","d":"will find","answer":"4","explain":"- Will find-> have found","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"I will not able to go to the art exhibit with you tonight because I am a bit under the weather.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"will not able","b":"to go","c":"a bit","d":"under","answer":"1","explain":"- Will not able-> will not be able","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"I may not have my problem to solve but at least I know I am on the right track.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"may not","b":"to solve","c":"at least","d":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- To solve-> solved","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Julia has to work very hard to make both ends to meet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"very hard","b":"to make","c":"both ends","d":"to meet","answer":"4","explain":"- To meet-> meet","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"When NASA decided to put a woman into space, none of the Sally's friends were surprised that they chose Sally.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to put","b":"into","c":"the","d":"that","answer":"3","explain":"- The-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"}]}